Elihu Thomson Papers 1865-1944 Mss.Ms.Coll.74
American Philosophical Society
- Series IX. Sketches, 1877-1933; 2 boxes; 1 linear feet
  - Meter. Type C direct current, 1902-1903, n.d.
  - Meters
    - Folder #1, 1882-1887
    - Folder #2, 1888-1910, n.d.
  - Miscellaneous
    - Folder #1, 1882-1889
    - Folder #2, 1890
    - Folder #3, 1891-1898
    - Folder #4, 1901-1912 (Box Series IX-2)
    - Folder #5, n.d.
  - Motors (a.c.). Control of, 9 Oct. 1909
  - N + O combination. Experiment in, 8 Dec. 1905
  - Pneumatic fire, 20 Jul. 1906
  - Power transmitter, 19-22 Jul. 1907
  - Power transmitting, 11 Jun. 1909
  - Projectile lubricator-forced, 8 Mar. 1910
  - Railways
    - Folder #1, 1888
    - Folder #2, 1889
    - Folder #3, 1890
    - Folder #4, n.d.
  - Rectifier, 19 Jan. 1909
  - Reed pipe, 5 Mar. 1906
  - Reed signal. Self-adjusting, 11 Apr. 1906
  - Refrigerator condensor, 14 Jan. 1926
  - Regulated-vulcanizing vise, 15 Oct. 1908
  - Resistances with large negative temperature coefficient, 5 Feb. 1909
  - Rice, E.W., Jr. Sketches of
    - Folder #1, 1882-1889
    - Folder #2, 1890-1893
    - Folder #3, n.d.
  - Safety devices, 1881-1889, n.d.
  - Series battery or accumulator, 15 Dec. 1911
  - Ship propulsion, 11 Oct. 1909
  - Sketch book [misc.]
    -See Ser. VIII, Sketch book [misc.]
  - Slow feed-toggle joint spring-multiplied lift
    -See Ser.XI for photograph
  - Speed changing device, 31 Mar. 1906
  - Speedometer, 2 Oct. 1909
  - Storage batteries, 15 Dec. 1911
  - Storage battery, 3 May 1912
  - Storage systems, 1883-1888, n.d.
  - Superheater at entrance to turbine. Arrangement of, 31 Mar. 1905
  - Switches, fuses and cut-outs, 1882-1889, n.d.
  - System of electric distribution
    -See Ser.XI for photographs
  - Systems regulation
    - Folder #1, 1879-1886
    - Folder #2, 1887-1890, n.d.
  - Tachometer modification, 16 Aug. 1907
  - Telescope and lenses, 1910, n.d.
  - Thermo-couple, 10 Dec. 1909
  - Thermo electric couple, 16 Feb. 1909
  - Three coil armature invention, Jul. 1933
  - Three coil machine, n.d.
  - Torpedo guidance by light beam, 25 Nov. 1908
  - Transformers, 1887-1889, n.d.
  - Turbine emergency (over speed) cut off, 7 Dec. 1905
  - Turbine generators. Short circuit slip for, 24 Feb. 1906
  - Wedge welding, 7 Dec. 1909
  - Welding and heating
    - Folder #1, 1886-1888
    - Folder #2, 1889-1890, n.d.
  - Welding sheet to sheet, 15 Feb. 1910
  - [Wightman, Merle J.?]. Sketch by
- Series X. Comments on Patents, 4 boxes; 2 linear feet
  Thomson's manuscript comments and notes on his patents. Originally bound in five volumes, comments are now arranged chronologically (by date patent was issued) on individual 8" x 10" sheets of paper. Each patent comment appears on a single page which has been laminated with Japanese tissue and is filed in a separate folder. Patents have been assigned identifying numbers which appear at the top of each patent comment and on a typescript list which duplicates the chronological arrangement of the series. This list is located in Box 1, Folder 1. Folders 2-4 in Box 1 contain typescript versions of the manuscript patent comments, and also follow the same chronological arrangement of the series (these typescripts exist for "vols. II-V;" "vol. I" is missing).
  In these patent comments, Thomson describes and evaluates each invention, often detailing the slight variations and improvements in newer versions. Thomson continued to work on some devices for years; consequently, he held many patents for mechanical apparatus such as dynamos, electric lighting systems, meters, and lamps. Initials at the top of each patent comment sheet appear to refer to the individuals, often besides Thomson, who worked on the patent. Edwin J. Houston and E.W. Rice, Jr. most often appear as collaborators on these inventions.
  Only three patent certificates issued to Thomson by the United States Patent Office have been preserved in this collection. They date ca. 1879 and are filed in Series XII, Certificates.
  - List of patents, 1876-1930 (Box Series X-1)
  - Typescripts of patents, vol.II, 1889-1893
  - Typescripts of patents, vol.III, 1893-1897
  - Typescripts of patents, vol.IV, 1898-1912
  - Typescripts of patents, vol.V, 1912-1930
  - Street railway rail fastener, 9 May 1876
  - Relays and sounders, 10 Oct. 1876
  - Dynamo electric machine, 2 Sep. 1879
  - Regulator for electric lamps, 7 Oct. 1879
  - Galvanic battery cell, 14 Oct. 1879
  - Regulator for electric lamps, 14 Oct. 1879
  - Process and app. for storage of electricity, 28 Oct. 1879
  - Dynamo electric machine, 13 Jan. 1880
  - Regulator for electric lamp, 20 Jan. 1880
  - Arm[ature] and com[mutator] for mag[netic] el[ectric] machines, 20 Jan. 1880
  - Aut[omatic] adj[uster] for com[mutator] brushes on mag[netic] electric machines, 20 Jan. 1880
  - Dynamo electric machine, 5 Oct. 1880
  - Dynamo electric machine, 5 Oct. 1880
  - Cur[rent] reg[ulator] for dynamo electric machine, 1 Mar. 1881
  - Centrifugal creamer, 5 Apr. 1881
  - Com[mutator]s for dynamo el[ectric] machine, 7 Jun. 1881
  - Electro magnetic device, 29 Nov. 1881
  - Electric lamp, 6 Dec. 1881
  - Electric lamp, 21 Feb. 1882
  - System of electric distribution, 4 Apr. 1882
  - Electric lamp, 18 Apr. 1882
  - Electric arc lamp, 30 May 1882
  - Electric arc lamp, 11 Jul. 1882
  - Electric arc lamp, 25 Jul. 1882
  - Means for preventing flashing between electric conductors, 10 Oct. 1882
  - Reg[ulator] for dynamo electric machines, 10 Oct. 1882
  - Electric arc light, 17 Oct. 1882
  - Dynamo electric machine, 26 Dec. 1882
  - Reg[ulator] for dynamo electric machine, 26 Dec. 1882
  - Commutator for dynamo electric machines, 6 Feb. 1883
  - Electric current regulator, 6 Feb. 1883
  - Electro magnetic retarding device, 13 Feb. 1883
  - Electric arc lamp, 27 Feb. 1883
  - Air blast attachment for commutators of dynamo electric machines, 6 Mar. 1883
  - Electric arc lamp, 20 Mar. 1883
  - Safety self-closing shunt switch for electric light circuits, 3 Apr. 1883
  - Safety self-closing shunt switch for electric light circuits, 3 Apr. 1883
  - Dynamo electric machine, 17 Jul. 1883
  - Electric com[mutator] or switch, 14 Aug. 1883
  - Electric lamp, 14 Aug. 1883
  - Electric lamp, 21 Aug. 1883
  - Safety device for electric arc lamps, 4 Dec. 1883
  - Dynamo electric machine, 26 Feb. 1884
  - Electric power distributing system, 26 Feb. 1884
  - Double carbon arc lamp, 25 Mar. 1884
  - Dynamo electric machine, 8 Apr. 1884
  - Dynamo electric machine, 15 Apr. 1884
  - Electric arc lamp, 22 Apr. 1884; 8 Folders
  - Electric lamp, 5 Aug. 1884
  - Focusing electric arc lamp, 5 Aug. 1884
  - Electric arc lamp, 5 Aug. 1884
  - Reg[ulator] for dynamo electric machines, 5 Aug. 1884
  - Electric arc lamp, 19 Aug. 1884
  - Electric lamp mechanism, 19 Aug. 1884
  - Electric lamp mechanism, 16 Sep. 1884
  - Electric arc lamp, 7 Oct. 1884; 2 Folders
  - Aut[omatic] cut-out for el[ectric] app[aratus], 11 Nov. 1884
  - Cut-out for electric arc lamps, 11 Nov. 1884
  - Cut-out for electric circuits, 16 Jun. 1885
  - Electric lamp, 16 Jun. 1885
  - Electric lighting system, 7 Jul. 1885
  - Electric switch, 7 Jul. 1885
  - Lightning arrester, 7 Jul. 1885
  - System of electrical distribution, 14 Jul. 1885; 2 Folders
  - Dynamo el[ectric] or el[ectric] dynamo machine, 11 Aug. 1885
  - Automatic commutator adjuster for dynamo electric machines, 11 Aug. 1885
  - Reg[ulator] for dynamo electric machines, 18 Aug. 1885
  - Electric arc lamp, 18 Aug. 1885
  - Safety device for electric circuits, 29 Sep. 1885
  - Dynamo electric machine, 5 Jan. 1886 (Box Series X-2)
  - Incandescent electric lamp, 2 Feb. 1886
  - System of electric distribution, 2 Feb. 1886
  - Incandescent electric lamp, 2 Feb. 1886
  - Electric motor, 2 Feb. 1886
  - Switch or turn-off for electric circuits, 2 Feb. 1886
  - Aut[omatic] cut-out for electric lamps, 16 Mar. 1886
  - Reg[ulator] for dynamo electric machines, 30 Mar. 1886
  - Electric switch, 13 Apr. 1886
  - Holder for incandescent lamps, 29 Jun. 1886
  - Electro magnetic motor, 13 Jul. 1886
  - Socket for incandescent lamps, 13 Jul. 1886
  - Commutator brush, 13 Jul. 1886
  - Apparatus for electric welding, 10 Aug. 1886; 2 Folders
  - Electric welding, 10 Aug. 1886
  - Compound wound dynamo electric machine, 28 Sep. 1886
  - Cut-out app[aratus] for electric lamps, 19 Oct. 1886
  - Aut[omatic] compensator for magnets, 19 Oct. 1886
  - Electro magnet, 19 Oct. 1886
  - Distribution of electric currents, 19 Oct. 1886
  - Regulator for electric currents, 23 Nov. 1886
  - Regulator for dynamo electric machines, motors, etc., 23 Nov. 1886
  - App[aratus] for the distribution of electricity by means of secondary batteries, 14 Dec. 1886
  - Re[gulator] for dynamo electric machines, 14 Dec. 1886
  - Induction coil, 14 Dec. 1886
  - Armature for dynamo electric machines, 1 Feb. 1887
  - Electric arc lamp, 1 Feb. 1887
  - Pump for producing high vacua, 22 Feb. 1887
  - System of electric distribution, 29 Mar. 1887
  - Electro magnetic cut-off, 29 Mar. 1887
  - Automatic cut-off, 29 Mar. 1887
  - System of electric distribution, 29 Mar. 1887
  - Electric switch, 17 May 1887
  - Automatic commutator adjuster, 17 May 1887
  - Alternating current electric motor, 17 May 1887
  - Alternating current motor device, 17 May 1887
  - Electric arc lamp, 28 Jun. 1887
  - System of electric distribution, 2 Aug. 1887
  - Reg[ulator] for dynamo electric machines and motors, 2 Aug. 1887
  - Coupling compound wound dynamo machines, 2 Aug. 1887
  - Coupling dynamo electric machines, 9 Aug. 1887
  - Dynamo electric machine or motor, 13 Sep. 1887
  - Electric arc lamp, 27 Sep. 1887
  - Reg[ulating] device for alternating circuits, 27 Sep. 1887
  - System of electric distribution for alternating currents, 1 Nov. 1887
  - Electric motor, 15 Nov. 1887
  - Electric welding, 20 Dec. 1887
  - Apparatus for electric welding, 3 Jan. 1888
  - Dynamo electric machine or motor, 10 Jan. 1888
  - Alternating current motor and regulating device, 31 Jan. 1888
  - Electric meter, 17 Apr. 1888
  - Electro-mechanical device, 17 Apr. 1888
  - Electric meter, 17 Apr. 1888
  - Alternating current dynamo electric machine, 8 May 1888
  - Alternating current regulator, 8 May 1888
  - Apparatus for electric welding, 26 Jun. 1888
  - Joining pipes by electricity, 3 Jul. 1888
  - Electricity welding chains and links, 3 Jul. 1888
  - Direct electric welding machine, 3 Jul. 1888
  - Electric meter, 3 Jul. 1888
  - Apparatus for electric welding, 17 Jul. 1888
  - Flue for electric transformers, 31 Jul. 1888
  - Thermal device for varying electric resistance of currents, 11 Sep. 1888
  - Direct welding dynamo electric machine, 18 Sep. 1888
  - Alternating current dynamo, 2 Oct. 1888
  - Electric potential differentiator, 23 Oct. 1888
  - Dynamo electric machine, 13 Nov. 1888
  - Electric light pole, 20 Nov. 1888
  - Portable electric welding apparatus, 18 Dec. 1888
  - Electric meter, 25 Dec. 1888
  - Forming, brazing and welding of metals by electricity, 8 Jan. 1889
  - Electric forging, 8 Jan. 1889
  - Electric welding, 8 Jan. 1889
  - Apparatus for electric welding and working metals, 8 Jan. 1889
  - Electric pipe joining and pipe work, 8 Jan. 1889
  - Electric metal working, 8 Jan. 1889
  - Electric riveting, 8 Jan. 1889
  - Regulating and motive device for alternating currents, 12 Feb. 1889
  - Manufacturing screws and bolts by electricity, 5 Mar. 1889
  - Electric welding machine, 5 Mar. 1889
  - Electric metal working and welding machine, 5 Mar. 1889
  - Dynamo electric machine, 19 Mar. 1889
  - Alternating current inductor, 19 Mar. 1889
  - Apparatus for regulating current or potential in secondary of transformers, 2 Apr. 1889
  - Method of regulating current or potential in secondary of transformers, 9 Apr. 1889
  - Alternating current electric motor, 9 Apr. 1889
  - Induction coil and self-inductive apparatus, 9 Apr. 1889
  - Armature for dynamo electric machines, 9 Apr. 1889
  - Lightning arrester, 9 Apr. 1889
  - Distribution of electric currents, 16 Apr. 1889
  - Electric meter, 23 Apr. 1889
  - Method of electric welding and shaping of metals, 14 May 1889
  - Process of electric soldering, brazing and welding, 21 May 1889
  - Method of electric welding and brazing, 21 May 1889
  - Electric meter, 25 Jun. 1889
  - Alternating current electric motor, 30 Jul. 1889
  - Induction coil, 27 Aug. 1889
  - Reactive and induction coil, 3 Sep. 1889
  - Electric measuring instrument, 22 Oct. 1889
  - System of electrical distribution, 22 Oct. 1889
  - Conduit for electrical railways, 22 Oct. 1889
  - Iron and induction coil for alternating current transfer, 5 Nov. 1889
  - Electric welding clamp, 19 Nov. 1889
  - Electric meter, 26 Nov. 1889; 2 Folders
  - Electric transformers, 26 Nov. 1889
  - Electric meters, 3 Dec. 1889
  - Induction coil, transformer, etc., 10 Dec. 1889
  - Method of making collars on axels by electricity, 31 Dec. 1889
  - Lightning arrester, 31 Dec. 1889
  - Electric transformer, 28 Jan. 1890
  - Cut-out for incandescent lamps, 11 Feb. 1890
  - System of distribution for alternating currents, 11 Feb. 1890
  - Compound insulating layer for electric coils, 4 Mar. 1890
  - Field magnet for dynamos, 11 Mar. 1890
  - Electric valve controller, 25 Mar. 1890
  - Method of electric soldering, cementing, etc., 25 Mar. 1890
  - Apparatus for electric soldering and cementing, 25 Mar. 1890
  - Distribution of electric currents, 15 Apr. 1890
  - Cut-out, 15 Apr. 1890
  - Guard for electric railway trolleys, 15 Apr. 1890
  - Safety connection, 22 Apr. 1890
  - Dynamo electric machine, 22 Apr. 1890
  - Turn-off for alternating current circuits, 27 May 1890
  - Casing for induction coils, 27 May 1890
  - Electric meter, 27 May 1890
  - Alternating current magnetic device, 27 May 1890
  - System of electrical distribution, 27 May 1890
  - Incandescent lamp socket, 27 May 1890
  - Guard wire protector and lighting arrester for electric railways, 27 May 1890
  - Electric switch, 27 May 1890
  - Regulator for dynamo electric machines, 27 May 1890
  - Electro-magnetic cut-out for electric lamps, 17 Jun. 1890
  - Regulator for dynamo electric machines, 17 Jun. 1890
  - Alternating current motor, 17 Jun. 1890
  - Electric arc lamp, 17 Jun. 1890
  - Electric railway conductor, 1 Jul. 1890
  - Frog for overhead wires, 22 Jul. 1890
  - Method of working metals by electricity, 22 Jul. 1890
  - Welding of other dynamo, 22 Jul. 1890
  - Method of welding pipes by electricity, 22 Jul. 1890
  - Electric meter, 22 Jul. 1890
  - Dynamo electric machine, 22 Jul. 1890
  - Manufacture of bands, rings, etc. by electricity, 22 Jul. 1890
  - Electric power transmission, 19 Aug. 1890
  - Electric power system, 19 Aug. 1890
  - Process and apparatus for forming and welding metals by electricity, 19 Aug. 1890
  - Induction discharge protector for welding apparatus, 19 Aug. 1890
  - Process of electric welding, 19 Aug. 1890
  - Section insulator for overhead electric conductors, 26 Aug. 1890
  - Suspending device for overhead electric conductors, 2 Sep. 1890
  - Electric motor, 14 Oct. 1890
  - Electric motor, 21 Oct. 1890
  - Process of electric welding, 21 Oct. 1890
  - Electric welding of pipes, 21 Oct. 1890
  - Electric arc lamp, 18 Nov. 1890; 2 Folders
  - Method of electric welding, 18 Nov. 1890
  - Trolley arm for electric railways, 18 Nov. 1890
  - Lightning arrester, 13 Jan. 1891
  - Electric arc lamp, 20 Jan. 1891
  - Method of electric welding, 20 Jan. 1891; 3 Folders
  - Incandescent electric lamp, 20 Jan. 1891
  - System of distributing and metering electric energy, 20 Jan. 1891
  - Electric meter, 20 Jan. 1891
  - Method of electric welding, 20 Jan. 1891
  - Electric railway conductor, 17 Feb. 1891
  - Electric arc lamp, 3 Mar. 1891
  - Dynamo electric motor or generator, 3 Mar. 1891
  - Electric lighting system, 17 Mar. 1891
  - Electric meter, 17 Mar. 1891
  - Electric meter, 24 Mar. 1891
  - Manufacturing chains by electric welding process, 31 Mar. 1891
  - Burr preventer for electric welding machines, 31 Mar. 1891
  - Electric arc lamp, 7 Apr. 1891
  - Method of electric welding, 7 Apr. 1891
  - Railroad gate crossing for overhead trains, 21 Apr. 1891
  - Method of electric welding, 28 Apr. 1891
  - Armature for dynamo electric machines or motors, 26 May 1891
  - Transformer, 16 Jun. 1891
  - Lightning arrester, 23 Jun. 1891; 3 Folders
  - Lamp cut-out and system, 23 Jun. 1891
  - Apparatus for removing inductive effects from electric lines, 30 Jun. 1891
  - Method of electric welding, 7 Jul. 1891
  - Securing metal bands on wooden or other articles, 7 Jul. 1891
  - Automatic hammer, 14 Jul. 1891
  - Method of measuring electric currents, 21 Jul. 1891
  - Electric motor for street cars, 4 Aug. 1891
  - Electric arc lamp, 18 Aug. 1891
  - Method of electric bending and straightening, 18 Aug. 1891
  - Electric motor, 1 Sep. 1891
  - Dynamo electric machine and motor, 15 Sep. 1891
  - System of eletrical distribution, 15 Sep. 1891
  - Composition for insulating material, 6 Oct. 1891
  - Electric arc lamp, 13 Oct. 1891
  - Adjustable transformer, 20 Oct. 1891
  - Mode of making tools, 27 Oct. 1891
  - Incandescent lamp, 3 Nov. 1891; 2 Folders
  - Brush holder for dynamo electric machines, 10 Nov. 1891
  - Armature core for dynamo electric machines, 24 Nov. 1891
  - Section insulator and lightning arrester for electric railroads, 24 Nov. 1891
  - Electric arc interrupter, 24 Nov. 1891
  - Lightning arrester, 8 Dec. 1891
  - Method of controlling alternating current induction, 15 Dec. 1891
  - Commutator for dynamo electric machines and motor, 19 Jan. 1892 (Box Series X-3)
  - Electric switch, 2 Feb. 1892
  - Method of and means for interrupting electric currents, 2 Feb. 1892
  - Dynamo electric machine, 2 Feb. 1892
  - System of electric distribution, 2 Feb. 1892
  - System of electrical distribution, 2 Feb. 1892
  - Lightning arrester, 9 Feb. 1892
  - Electric railway, 2 Mar. 1892
  - Lightning arrester, 15 Mar. 1892
  - Alternating current motor, 22 Mar. 1892
  - Safety device for electric motors, 7 Jun. 1892
  - Dynamo electric machine, 7 Jun. 1892
  - Manufacture of axes, 14 Jun. 1892
  - Electric arc lamp, 5 Jul. 1892
  - Distribution of electric currents, 12 Jul. 1892
  - Method of electric soldering, 9 Aug. 1892
  - System of telephony, 30 Aug. 1892
  - Induction coil for electric meters, 6 Sep. 1892
  - Ventilating armatures for dynamo electric machines, 13 Sep. 1892
  - Armature for dynamos and motors, 4 Oct. 1892
  - Regulator for dynamo electric machines, 1 Nov. 1892
  - Continuous current transformer, 8 Nov. 1892
  - Electric transformer, 29 Nov. 1892
  - Method of electric welding, 6 Dec. 1892
  - Electric arc lamp, 27 Dec. 1892
  - Electric arc lamp, 3 Jan. 1893
  - Electric circuit breaker, 17 Jan. 1893
  - Armature for dynamo electric machines or motor, 24 Jan. 1893
  - Thermal circuit closer, 31 Jan. 1893
  - Dynamo electric machine, 14 Mar. 1893
  - Lightning arrester, 14 Mar. 1893
  - Electric arc lamp, 21 Mar. 1893
  - Compressed air apparatus, 11 Apr. 1893
  - Lightning arrester, 18 Apr. 1893; 2 Folders
  - Electric soldering, 25 Apr. 1893
  - System of electric distribution, 25 Apr. 1893
  - Electric lighting system, 2 May 1893
  - Commutator for dynamo electric machines, 2 May 1893
  - Friction coupling for dynamos or motors, 2 May 1893
  - Safety connection for induction coil systems, 9 May 1893
  - Commutator brush holder for dynamo electric machines, 16 May 1893
  - Safety appliance for systems of electric distribution, 23 May 1893
  - Pole piece for dynamo electric machines, 30 May 1893
  - Electric switch, 4 Jul. 1893
  - Method of and means for producing alternating currents, 4 Jul. 1893
  - Rheostat, 4 Jul. 1893
  - Lightning arrester, 11 Jul. 1893
  - Manufacture of incandescent electric lamps, 11 Jul. 1893
  - Automatic chain welding machine, 18 Jul. 1893
  - Shaping and spinning metals by electricity, 18 Jul. 1893
  - Electric measuring instrument, 25 Jul. 1893
  - Fusible cut-out, 1 Aug. 1893
  - Regulator for electric generators, 8 Aug. 1893
  - Method of winding coils for dynamo electric armatures, 15 Aug. 1893
  - Cut-out, 10 Oct. 1893
  - System of electrical distribution, 14 Nov. 1893
  - Electric lighting system, 14 Nov. 1893
  - Lightning arrester, 14 Nov. 1893
  - Protection for the insulation of dynamo electric machines, 14 Nov. 1893
  - Electrical transformer, 14 Nov. 1893
  - Contact apparatus, 14 Nov. 1893
  - Electric cut-out, 14 Nov. 1893
  - Insulating composition, 14 Nov. 1893
  - Cooling transformer, 14 Nov. 1893
  - Electric transformer, 14 Nov. 1893
  - Electric arc lamp, 14 Nov. 1893
  - Reactive coil, 14 Nov. 1893
  - Dynamo electric machine or motor, 14 Nov. 1893
  - Leading-in wire for incandescent lamps, 14 Nov. 1893
  - Detector for electric current meters, 14 Nov. 1893
  - Electric meter, 14 Nov. 1893
  - Indicating apparatus for electric circuit, 14 Nov. 1893
  - Regulator for dynamo electric machines, 28 Nov. 1893
  - Method and means for compounding dynamo electric machines, 26 Dec. 1893
  - Electric measuring instrument, 26 Dec. 1893
  - Chain making machine, 16 Jan. 1894
  - Means for neutralizing self induction in alternating circuits, 23 Jan. 1894
  - Electric furnace, 30 Jan. 1894
  - Electric railway system, 20 Mar. 1894
  - Method of constructing commutators for dynamos or motors, 20 Mar. 1894
  - Regulation of alternating currents, 20 Mar. 1894
  - Means for regulating alternating currents, 20 Mar. 1894
  - Armature winding, 20 Mar. 1894
  - Alternating current electric motor, 20 Mar. 1894
  - Electrical transformer, 20 Mar. 1894
  - Armature for dynamo electric machines, 17 Apr. 1894
  - Mode of cooling electric motors, 17 Apr. 1894
  - System of electrical distribution, 1 May 1894
  - Means for preventing arcing in electric power stations, 5 Jun. 1894
  - Electric reciprocating motor, 5 Jun. 1894
  - Electric motor, 5 Jun. 1894
  - Meter for recording measurements of electric power, 19 Jun. 1894
  - Electric meter, 19 Jun. 1894
  - Alternating current dynamo electric machine, 3 Jul. 1894
  - Current interrupter for high potential circuits, 10 Jul. 1894
  - Commutator for dynamo electric machines, 17 Jul. 1894
  - Electro expansion device, 31 Jul. 1894
  - Dynamo electric machine, 31 Jul. 1894
  - Electric arc lamp, 28 Aug. 1894; 2 Folders
  - Electric lighting system and apparatus, 4 Sep. 1894
  - Electric motor, 18 Sep. 1894
  - Electric transformer, 30 Oct. 1894
  - Electric incandescent lamp, 20 Nov. 1894
  - Electric welding apparatus, 22 Jan. 1895
  - Electric meter, 22 Jan. 1895
  - Dynamo electric machine, 12 Feb. 1895
  - Carbon for arc lamps, 12 Feb. 1895
  - Means for operating drills, 26 Feb. 1895
  - Method and means for preventing magnetic leakage, 26 Feb. 1895
  - Incandescent electric lamp, 16 Apr. 1895
  - Electric measuring instrument, 16 Apr. 1895; 3 Folders
  - Carbon brush, 21 May 1895; 2 Folders
  - Electric meter, 26 May 1895
  - Brush holder for dynamo electric machines, 28 May 1895
  - Transformer for alternating current systems, 9 Jul. 1895
  - Electric arc lamp, 16 Jul. 1895
  - Electric measuring instrument, 16 Jul. 1895
  - Electric current distributer, 23 Jul. 1895
  - System of electric distribution, 6 Aug. 1895
  - Winding of dynamo electric machines or motors, 13 Aug. 1895
  - Means for synchronizing electric motors, 27 Aug. 1895
  - Alternating current generator or motor, 13 Sep. 1895
  - Dynamo electric machine, 22 Oct. 1895
  - Dynamo electric machine, 26 Nov. 1895
  - Electric safety device, 3 Dec. 1895
  - Electric arc lamp, 24 Dec. 1895
  - Electrical measuring instrument, 11 Feb. 1896
  - Electric welding indicator, 25 Feb. 1896
  - Electric riveting, 25 Feb. 1896
  - Electric motor, 25 Feb. 1896
  - Monocyclic generator, 3 Mar. 1896
  - Electric measuring instrument, 19 Mar. 1896
  - Rotary transformer, 14 Jul. 1896